[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Many credit this book by Rachel Carson with launching the environmentalist movement.", "correct_answer": "Silent Spring", "incorrect_answers": ["Soft Spring", "White Spring", "Our Spring"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The incredibles was a term used during the production of 747 referring to what?", "correct_answer": "The rugged team of workers", "incorrect_answers": ["The airlines which put downpayments and helped jumpstart the project", "The significant others of the workers", "The 20 000 contractors helping Boeing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many eyelids do camels have on each of their eyes?", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "4", "5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This person, who died in 1997, was verified by Guiness World Records as the shortest man on earth?", "correct_answer": "Gul Mohammed", "incorrect_answers": ["Younis Edwan", "He Pingping", "Lin Yu-chih"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played keyboards on the Beach Boys hits?", "correct_answer": "Darryl Dragon", "incorrect_answers": ["Pete  McIntosch", "Mike Love", "Stan Gibb"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many species of zebra are known to exist?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["6", "3", "5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the river in which Jesus Christ was baptized by John the Baptist?", "correct_answer": "The Jordan", "incorrect_answers": ["The Tigris", "The Euphrates", "The Nile"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bratwurst is often consumed in this country.  They are sausages made of pork and veal and seasoned with ginger, nutmeg, and coriander or caraway.", "correct_answer": "Germany", "incorrect_answers": ["Macedonia", "Hungary", "Romania"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the leader of the first squad of Shinsengumi?", "correct_answer": "Okita S\u014dji", "incorrect_answers": ["Inoue Genzabur\u014d", "Harada Sanosuke", "T\u014dd\u014d Heisuke"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the unsinkable Molly Brown in the movie Titanic?", "correct_answer": "Kathy Bates", "incorrect_answers": ["Gloria Stuart", "Kate Winslet", "Frances Fischer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The album Paint it Black by the Rolling Stones was released in this year.", "correct_answer": "1966", "incorrect_answers": ["1962", "1978", "1974"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular Texas city was The Texas Chainsaw Massacre filmed in?", "correct_answer": "Austin", "incorrect_answers": ["San Antonio", "Houston", "Dallas"]}]